FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
IMPORTANT PERSON
Were you okay?
Huh?
With what I said, I mean.
- Oh, uh...
Let me hold it. It's a
boyfriend privilege.
Boyfriend?
All right, got it!
Ahh, no! It should really be my
privilege, since... I'm the one receiving
- help.
- Don't be silly.
The privilege is all mine... ...Kuronuma.
Because of that...
... here...
Actually... I-If you don't mind...
...I'll keep this one.
So, that way...
...we can go throw them away together.
I'm sorry I said that
in front of everyone.
I was done hiding it... ...so
before it become a rumor...
...I thought I should
make it perfectly clear...
I wanted people to know I really like you.
And that we're dating.
I... didn't want this to
get more complicated.
That's why...
Wait! Actually... I already told you my
feelings in front of everyone. But it's
not like that was how
I planned on doing it.
I'm sorry if I embarrassed you...
It made me...
...so happy.
He's trying to express his feelings...
...so that they're clear
to me and everyone else.
Well, I'm glad.
Are you two acting out a dating sim
while taking out the trash?! And what's
with this sparkly background?!
Shoo! Shoo! Get outta here!
Come with me, Shota!
You're taking Miura's
place! Time to clean!
Kazehaya! You can't tag
along, it defeats the whole point!
Listen up... -It's time for you to learn
that however many ups there are in life,
there are just as many
downs. -Sorry, Kuronuma!
So what people were
saying was really true.
- Wait... what?
- I'm shocked.
- I refuse to believe it.
- Kazehaya just wanted a
- girlfriend. That's all it is.
- Yeah.
I'm sure they'll break up soon.
My position...
And my feelings...
- Those two are officially dating now.
- It makes me feel kinda lonely.
I'm honestly glad no one's come out
to attack Sawako over this whole thing.
- Yeah.
- And no one's tried to mess with
- her like that one group did before.
- That's true.
If anything, there may be
some girls crying in secret.
Yeah, I can definitely
understand having a reaction like that.
- Look, it's not what you think.
- None of it means we think
you're to blame for any of that!
No, I know you're right.
I was overjoyed,
because it felt like a dream.
Kazehaya's face kept
showing up in my mind.
But what showed up next...
...was Kurumi's face.
Not only her... but the many other
people who were shocked by it.
All of their feelings are the exact
same as mine from not that long ago.
And I'm fully aware that they're
something produced because of the position
- I'm in now.
- I got rejected... but I
clearly told him my feelings.
If she never said those words...
If she was never there...
I think you mean rivals.
Sawa...
- I'm sorry, I need to go.
- Wait a sec, going where?!
Let her go, Chizu.
She's gonna see Kurumi.
Sawako!
I'll say this only 'cause I get how she
feels. There isn't anything you can do
about how it ended up for her.
You're not to blame.
Just don't forget that, okay?
- And I know... she's gotta get her closure.
- Chizu sure does love
her closure, doesn't she?
- Yeah.
- His girlfriend? Seriously?
That rumor's been around for a while.
If we knew this was gonna happen,
we would've been tougher on her.
Do you guys think we should let her know?
Gonna tell us what's so funny, Kurumi?
This is why Kazehaya never liked you.
- Are you trying to pick a fight?
- In case you've forgotten, you were
the one who started Sadako's rumor!
And then you used us to
benefit yourself didn't you?
- Yeah, and?
- The five of you were the perfect pawns.
Since you seemed
basically as rotten as I was.
It's too hard for you to ask Kazehaya
out yourself, so you pick on Sawako
- because it's a lot easier.
- Excuse me? You're no different than us!
Yeah, you're right.
Everyone but Sawako is just the same.
Kurumi...
Sadako!
So, are the rumors
about Kazehaya real or fake?
- They just can't be true!
- I don't believe it!
- Are you blackmailing him?!
- Uh, I don't...
I bet Yano and Yoshida helped you!
Why would he choose someone
like you, when he could have--
Shut up!
Give it a rest already.
Isn't it pathetic to still complain at
this point? This is what Kazehaya chose.
What? Who do you think you are?
You think you're in a position to say
that? After everything you did?! -You know
what'll happen if we tell him,
don't you? -Go ahead and do it...
If you don't care what he thinks of you
after doing that then be my guest! He'll
ask you why you even brought it up.
And then see right through your ulterior
motives. He despises people who snitch on
others just for their
own benefit. Understand?
And to add to that...
if you do anything to Sawako...
You're done for. He won't forgive you.
And I... know that for a fact.
Get back here! I'm not done talking to--
Since I'm already her
rival... I'll talk to her.
What... Hey! Don't get carried
away just because you're his--
- Yo!
- Y-Yoshida.
- So, you still like Kazehaya, huh?
- Yeah, I still do. What about it?
Hold on a minute, does
this mean you all liked him?
- And why'd it have to be Sadako?
- I can't believe he's
taken by somebody now!
Huh?! You can't be
serious? Why didn't you tell me?!
"Why"?
Because we felt bad.
Y-You didn't know this beforehand?
Now, tell me...
Would you have given up easier if it was
Kurumi? Or would it have been better if
Kazehaya had picked
one of you guys instead?
Either of those still would have been
hard, right? There's nothing wrong with
you guys still liking him.
But having said that, liking him for
a long time doesn't make you better.
If you never take action...
You'll never get closure.
The regret you're feeling is
because you didn't do anything.
So isn't it messed up to complain
to Sawako while ignoring that fact?
And besides, Kazehaya
said this is a like a drea--
Before all of this happened the way it
did, I'm pretty sure none of you had any
sort of problem with Sawako.
You just liked Kazehaya. And
that's all there was to it...
Regardless of his reputation or anything.
Well, that's probably the same with
Kazehaya. He's not the kinda guy to choose
someone based on reputation, right?
I imagine you came to like him because
that's the way he is. But I don't need to
tell you that since you already know.
You're angry, but still, you all
want him to be happy don't you?
It's complicated.
There's no need to be
stubborn. Why not let it all out?
And don't do it for Kazehaya...
Do it for yourself.
P.E. TEACHER'S OFFICE
Hey, Shota. Way to go.
I mean, you helped.
Huh? But I don't think
I really did anything.
No, you lent me an ear--
Where's my thanks?
Well, Shota?
No matter how you look at it, I'm the MVP
here. I deserve a nice, "Thank you very
much!"
Yeah, you're right.
Despite everything, you actually did
help me to think through all that stuff
so... ...thanks.
Yeah, exactly!
And! Wanna know somethin'? I was also
giving Kuronuma some helpful advice behind
- your back at the exact same time!
- Who even asked you to do that?!
Please... don't give Kuronuma
any more unnecessary advice.
Huh?
I want to take care of her, seriously.
I'm happy for ya, Shota. You were able to
squeeze out your measly feelings for her.
You not listening, are you?
Hey, kiddo...
When it comes to romance, only the
person who asks someone out first, can
fight against their true love.
And the people who are second, third, or
beyond that, aren't even qualified for it.
Which means...
Whenever Kuronuma's true love shows up,
you're really gonna have to prove
- yourself.
- What are you talking about?
Shota... Hang in there.
What?
I... finally told my feelings to Kazehaya.
And we've decided to date.
Okay? Did you come here to brag?
If she were in my place, I'm sure
she would've done the same thing.
I told you, I'll never
say, "I'm happy for you."
I know it. She'd have done it for me.
Anything else?
No.
Just wanted... you to know.
Sawako.
Do you remember?
When I had mentioned that
"I made sure to tell him"?
It was only because you were there.
I think that if you hadn't been...
Then, I... would've never been
able to tell him my true feelings.
Despite getting rejected.
I'm glad...
...that you were my rival.
PLUM JUICE
You know... I overheard that
Your conversation with Sadako.
Your point?
Well, I just thought it
was surprising, is all.
That's true. It looked like she
was prepared to get told off by me.
- And I intended to do so.
- Oh. Really?
But she didn't say anything. It was weird.
If she had said, "Thank you," or,
"I'm sorry," or something, I was honestly
- thinking of kicking her butt.
- Here's a question for you... what if I
went out with Sadako? What are your
thoughts on something like that?
You're not good enough. That's mean.
But neither am I.
If Kazehaya liked me, he
would've asked me out a long time ago.
Didn't matter how hard I tried.
In fact, whenever he was with her...
...he acted completely different.
I never knew he could
make a face like that.
Or that he could even
behave the way he did.
It's obvious now.
There's absolutely no chance Kazehaya
will ever like me from this point forward.
I did the one thing that he hates the
most... and could never forgive me for.
To be honest, he couldn't handle you.
Y'know, truthfully, if I
liked girls, you'd be my type.
I mean it I know I could
understand you. Even all your darker
sides.
I don't need... sympathy.
When I realized that this was finally
going to be over... I felt a bit relieved.
Oh yeah the whole thing surprised me...
Kazehaya was head over heels for Sadako.
And Kurumi was more awkward than I thought
she'd be.
On the flip side, Sadako was cuter than I
thought. Although, the biggest surprise
was me thinking, "I'm glad this all
happened before I started liking her."
Are you for real?!
Yeah, sure am.
I'm gonna need you to promise you
won't mess with her anymore, you got it?
Don't worry, I promise!
- What's that supposed to mean?
- I... couldn't say anything.
There was nothing that felt
right to say in that moment.
If it'd been me I
probably would've done the same.
There's nothing you really can say to her.
It's because of Kurumi...
If she wasn't there then...
I wouldn't have had such a good rival.
And that's how I really feel.
But I know this isn't
something I should say out loud.
Ryu!
- See ya later, Sawa!
- Why?
Just come on!
- See ya, Shota.
- Later...
Oh. Now I get it.
- Glad you figured it out.
- Yeah. By the way, Chizuru.
I like you.
- What the... Ryu! You surprised me!
- Thought you should know.
You big dummy! I already know!
There are all kinds of feelings... for
all kinds of people... in many situations...
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah.
Kazehaya!
Huh?
Nevermind...
It's nothing.
I'm glad... that you were my rival.
I'll treat him well.
I'll do my best